cracku.in 2016-12-21

# Cracku | Privacy Policy

We, Chaya Education Private Limited, the creator of this Privacy Policy ensure our firm's commitment to your privacy vis-à-vis the protection of your priceless information. In order to endow you with our uninterrupted use of services, we may collect and, in some circumstances, disclose information about you. To enhance better protection of your privacy we provide this notice explaining our information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, you should Us at cracku@cracku.in

#### Overview

We commit to respecting your online privacy data. We further recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information **("Personal Information")** you share with us. Information that is considered personal about you by us includes, but is not limited to, your name, photo, address, email address or other contact information.

In order to use this website, you are required to login through Facebook or register an account using an email address. After your permission we will have access to details such as Name, Photos, Age, Gender, City, List of Friends etc, as provided for in the Terms of Use.

#### Notification of Modifications and Changes to the T&C and Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change the Terms and Privacy Policy from time to time as seen fit, without any intimation to you, and your continued use of the site will signify your acceptance of any amendment to these terms.

You are therefore advised to re-read the Terms of Service on a regular basis. Should it be that you do not accept any of the modifications or amendments to the Terms, you may terminate your use of this website immediately.

#### Information we collect

Our site's online requisition form requires users to log in through Facebook or register an account using an email address.

Certain information, such as your name, e-mail addresses, is collected in order to among other things, verify your identity, for use as account numbers in our record system, and to track your performance in the online tests. Email addresses, Intellectual Property, any information entered in any form displayed on any section of the website are also collected.

#### Cookies

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Websites. "Cookies" are small files stored on your hard drive that assists us in providing customized services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a "cookie". Cookies can also help us provide information targeted to your interests. Cookies may be used whether you register with us or not.

#### External Links on Website

The Website may include hyperlinks to other web sites or content or resources. We have no control over any websites or resources, which are provided by companies or persons other than Us.

You acknowledge and agree that We are not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources.

You acknowledge and agree that We are not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources. These third-party service providers and Third-Party Sites may have their own privacy policies governing the storage and retention of your personal information that you may be subject to. We recommend that when you enter a Third-Party Site, you review the Third Party Site's privacy policy as it relates to safeguarding your personal information. We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit the Website.

#### Our use of your information

Your contact information is used to contact you when necessary. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. Finally, we may use your IP address to help protect our partners and ourselves from fraud. We will continue to enhance our security procedures as new technology becomes available. We will transfer information about you if We are acquired by or merged with another company. Upon the occurrence of such an event, we will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may release your personal information to a third-party in order comply with a Court Order or other similar legal procedure, or when we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with the law, prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or investigate or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or violations of Our Terms of Service. We may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with our Intellectual Property Rights Policy as mentioned in the Terms of Use as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, We may disclose name, address, country, phone number, email address and company name.

#### Confidentiality

You hereby acknowledge that the Website may contain information which is designated confidential by Us and that you shall not disclose such information without our prior written consent.

Your information is regarded as confidential and therefore will not be divulged to any third party, except as set forth herein.

#### Our Disclosure of your Information

Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government, law enforcement agencies or third parties. Under certain circumstances, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, or members may abuse or misuse your information that they collect from our Website. Therefore, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications would always remain private.

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party.

 **Law and order:** We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties to enforce laws, such as: intellectual property rights, fraud and other rights. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement and other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate, in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal liability.

#### Accessing, Reviewing and Changing your profile

If you change any information on Facebook we may keep track of your old information. If you want us to stop tracking your Facebook ID please send us a mail at cracku@cracku.in.

We will retain in our files information you have requested to remove for certain circumstances, such as to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personally identifiable information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

#### Other information collectors

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent that you disclose your information to other parties, whether they are on our Websites or on other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. To the extent that we use third party advertisers, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of the third parties, you are subject to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

#### Security

We treat data as an asset that must be protected against loss and unauthorized access. We employ many different security techniques to protect such data from unauthorized access by members inside and outside the company. We do not recommend transfer of sensitive information (such as credit card number) and bank account details via the Site. Users are recommended to do so offline, on the phone or via personal emails. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and upon receipt.

#### Disclaimer

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personal information (including sensitive information like credit card information and bank account number) will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. Therefore, although we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will always remain private. As a user of the Site, you understand and agree that you assume all responsibility and risk for your use of the Site, the internet generally, and the documents you post or access and for your conduct on and off the Site.

Also, The Questions, Answers, Solutions and other Services on our Website are filtered through strict quality checks by experts in the field. However, Chaya Education Private Limited doesn't make any warranty (either implicit or explicit) that the Services are accurate or well fit for the users including you. The Services provided by Chaya Education Private Limited might be temporarily unavailable for time to time to provide for maintenance, up gradation of software or any other reason we deem fit. Chaya Education Private Limited reserves the right to not provide its Services to any person. In addition to the above, Chaya Education Private Limited doesn't provide any warranty that:

  1. The questions, answers, solutions, any other study material or Services provided by the Website are accurate and useful
  2. The Services provided by the website will be always be functional and operating
  3. The Services provided by the website will meet up your expectations and any changes sought by you will be implemented
  4. The pricing of the Services will not change from time to time
  5. The services are free of any typographical mistakes, inaccuracies or any other mistakes of any sort
